A Guide to the Foundation Center of New York records FA023
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative Files, 1922-2004; 1
  - Officer and Committee Files, 1922-1998; 2
    - Officer Files, 1922-1998; A
      - Thomas R. Buckman, 1957-1992; 5
        - The Foundation Directory - Complimentary Copies, 1971-1977 (Reel 44, Frame 376)
        - The Foundation Directory - Correspondence, 1971-1985 (Reel 44, Frame 416)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 5, 1972-1975 (Reel 44, Frame 447)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 6 - Introduction, 1976 (Reel 44, Frame 483)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 7 - Introduction, 1979 (Reel 44, Frame 536)
        - The Foundation Directory - Marketing, 1964-1972 (Reel 44, Frame 542)
        - The Foundation Directory - Publishing, 1968-1981 (Reel 44, Frame 550)
        - The Foundation Directory - Reception, 1975 (Reel 44, Frame 625)
        - The Foundation Luncheon Group - Energy Crisis, January 30, 1974 (Reel 44, Frame 661)
        - Foundation Managers, Inc., 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 678)
        - Foundation News, 1979-1985 (Reel 44, Frame 682)
        - Foundation News - Advisory Board, 1972 (Reel 44, Frame 708)
        - Foundation News - Reprint Permissions, 1971-1976 (Reel 44, Frame 720)
        - Foundation News Indexes - "Foundations: 20 Viewpoints", 1966-1971 (Reel 44, Frame 725)
        - Foundation Projects Reports, 1976-1977 (Reel 44, Frame 741)
        - Foundation Projects Reports - Power Proposal, 1975-1977 (Reel 44, Frame 770)
        - General Files, 1971-1997 (Reel 44, Frame 808)
        - Globe and National Examiner Tabloid Articles, 1982-1983 (Reel 44, Frame 928)
        - The Grant Foundation, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 44, Frame 1,005)
        - Grants Index, 1984 (Reel 44, Frame 1,030)
        - Grants Index - Proposals and Responses, 1971 (Reel 44, Frame 1,040)
        - Grantmaker Services, 1980-1983 (Reel 45, Frame 1)
        - Grantmaker Services and Custom Searching - History and Guidelines, 1983-1989 (Reel 45, Frame 21)
        - Grantmakers in Health, 1980-1987 (Reel 45, Frame 60)
        - The Grantmaker Center, 1984-1985 (Reel 45, Frame 152)
        - Harke Subcommittee - Senate Subcommittee on Foundations, 1973-1976 (Reel 45, Frame 165)
        - Hewlett-Packard Company Foundation, 1980-1983 (Reel 45, Frame 296)
        - House Subcommittee on Domestic Finance - Wright Patman, 1972-1973 (Reel 45, Frame 355)
        - Huenefeld Study, 1981-1992 (Reel 45, Frame 443)
        - Individual Grantseekers Referral, 1984 (Reel 45, Frame 543)
        - Information Systems Department, 1981-1986 (Reel 45, Frame 547)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Contacts and Procedures, 1979-1989 (Reel 45, Frame 568)
        - Interphil Collection Exchange, 1989-1991 (Reel 45, Frame 630)
        - Inventory of Videotape Equipment in METRO Libraries, 1973-1974 (Reel 45, Frame 663)
        - Investment Advisors - Selection Process, 1987 (Reel 45, Frame 726)
        - The Johnson Foundation - Wingspread Conference, July 23-25, 1986 (Reel 45, Frame 736)
        - Joint Committee on Functions, 1970-1971 (Reel 45, Frame 807)
        - Joint Committee on Research, 1972-1978 (Reel 45, Frame 864)
        - Junior Associates Program, 1985 (Reel 45, Frame 1,021)
        - Russell V. Kohr, 1973 (Reel 45, Frame 1,029)
        - Leases - Databases, 1974-1975 (Reel 45, Frame 1,082)
        - Marianna O. Lewis, 1983 (Reel 45, Frame 1,111)
        - Library Planning - Microforms, 1971 (Reel 45, Frame 1,122, Card 1, Card 8, Card 9, Card 10)
          See also corresponding microfiche cards.
        - Library Survey - C. Lee Jones, 1985-1987 (Reel 46, Frame 1)
        - Literature Project - An Information System for the Non-Profit Voluntary Sector, 1984-1986 (Reel 46, Frame 204)
        - Literature Project - Herner and Company Proposal, 1986 (Reel 46, Frame 279)
        - Literature Project - King Research, Inc., 1986-1990 (Reel 46, Frame 371)
        - Literature Project - Library Indexing Project, 1982-1983 (Reel 46, Frame 450)
        - Literature Project - Request for Proposals, 1985-1986 (Reel 46, Frame 545)
        - Literature Project - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Reel 46, Frame 653)
        - Mailing to College Presidents, 1972 (Reel 46, Frame 680)
        - Major Gift Campaign - Thomas R. Buckman - History, 1991-1993 (Reel 46, Frame 698)
        - Major Gift Campaign - History Notes, 1989-1992 (Reel 46, Frame 942)
        - Major Gift Campaign - Index, May 1988 (Reel 46, Frame 971)
        - Major Gift Campaign - Themes, Overviews and Chronology, 1989-1993 (Reel 46, Frame 974)
        - Marketing Reports, 1977-1981 (Reel 46, Frame 1,023)
        - Meeting With The Sloan Foundation and The Spencer Foundation, 1972-1974 (Reel 46, Frame 1,129)
        - The Charles E. Merrill Trust Book Project, 1984 (Reel 46, Frame 1,207)
        - Microfilming Corporation of America, 1969-1972 (Reel 47, Frame 1, Card 2, Card 3, Card 4, Card 5, Card 7)
        - Microfilming of Foundation News and Foundation Center Annual Reports, 1973-1991 (Reel 47, Frame 20)
        - Miscellaneous Cost Data and Income, 1975-1988 (Reel 47, Frame 40)
        - National Center for Charitable Statistics, 1983-1992 (Reel 47, Frame 77)
        - National Federation of Abstracting and Indexing, 1972-1979 (Reel 47, Frame 404)
        - National Institutes of Health, 1974-1976 (Reel 47, Frame 492)
        - National Taxonomy of Exempt Entities (NTEE), 1992-1993 (Reel 47, Frame 621)
        - National Taxonomy of Exempt Entities (NTEE) - Letters of Endorsement, 1989-1990 (Reel 47, Frame 776)
        - New Ideas Committee, 1984 (Reel 47, Frame 787)
        - New Office Reception, April 18, 1985 (Reel 47, Frame 862)
        - New York State Council on the Arts - Grants Project, 1972-1973 (Reel 47, Frame 892)
        - New York State Division for Youth - Project Proposal, 1982 (Reel 47, Frame 950)
        - The New York Times Book Review, 1976-1982 (Reel 47, Frame 960)
        - Nomination for the John W. Gardner Leadership Award, 1991-1992 (Reel 47, Frame 971)
        - Objectives, 1975 (Reel 47, Frame 1,005)
        - Open House, January 30, 1972 (Reel 47, Frame 1,015)
        - Overhead Policy, 1971-1972 (Reel 47, Frame 1,046)
        - Overseas Foundations, 1972-1976 (Reel 47, Frame 1,059)
        - Overseas Foundation - Charities Aid Fund, 1971-1975 (Reel 48, Frame 1)
        - Overseas Foundation - The Charity Commission, 1971-1975 (Reel 48, Frame 116)
        - Overseas Foundation - The Commonwealth Foundation, 1971-1977 (Reel 48, Frame 151)
        - Overseas Foundation - The Nuffield Foundation, 1971-1977 (Reel 48, Frame 162)
        - Panel of Consultants, 1970-1972 (Reel 48, Frame 193)
        - Peat Marwick Main Seminars, 1988-1989 (Reel 48, Frame 228)
        - Permissions Policy, 1983-1986 (Reel 48, Frame 238)
        - Philanthropy Literature Indexing - Proposal, 1982-1983 (Reel 48, Frame 260)
        - Planning Task Force - Five-Year Plan Update, 1986-1988 (Reel 48, Frame 297)
        - Policy on Charging for Services, 1972-1974 (Reel 48, Frame 394)
        - Richard L. Press, 1972-1973 (Reel 48, Frame 406)
        - Principal Staff, 1981-1987 (Reel 48, Frame 488)
        - "Private Foundation Information Returns, 1982" - Margaret Riley, 1982-1983 (Reel 48, Frame 506)
        - Program Goals, 1975-1981 (Reel 48, Frame 535)
        - Program Managers Meetings, 1987-1989 (Reel 48, Frame 551)
        - Proposed Merger of The Foundation Center and Council on Foundations, Inc., 1970-1971 (Reel 48, Frame 659)
        - Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1982 (Reel 48, Frame 776)
        - Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1987 (Reel 48, Frame 812)
        - Regional Collections, 1971-1980 (Reel 48, Frame 819)
        - Regional Collections - Depository Collections, 1971-1972 (Reel 48, Frame 970)
        - Regional Collections - Letters and Enclosures, 1973 (Reel 48, Frame 1,055)
        - Regional Collections - Mailings, 1973 (Reel 48, Frame 1,118)
        - Regional Collections - Planning, 1972-1974 (Reel 49, Frame 1)
        - Regional Collections Bulletin, 1975-1976 (Reel 49, Frame 107)
        - Regional Depositing Libraries - Orientation, May 8, 1972 (Reel 49, Frame 205)
        - Relocation, 1984-1985 (Reel 49, Frame 209)
        - Report on Programs and Services, 1977 (Reel 49, Frame 262)
        - Research Committee - Independent Sector, 1982-1990 (Reel 49, Frame 266)
        - Research Workshops, 1986 (Reel 49, Frame 295)
        - Reserve Fund Papers, 1967-1990 (Reel 49, Frame 305)
        - Responses to Fund-Raising Letters, 1972 (Reel 49, Frame 347)
        - Retirement Party, 1991 (Reel 49, Frame 396)
          Separated Materials
          See also audio cassette in Box 1, Folder 1.
        - Retreat, 1980 (Reel 49, Frame 398)
        - Retreat, 1981 (Reel 49, Frame 412)
        - Retreat, 1982 (Reel 49, Frame 428)
        - Retreat, 1983 (Reel 49, Frame 452)
        - Retreat, 1984 (Reel 49, Frame 518)
        - Retreat, 1985 (Reel 49, Frame 621)
        - Retreat, 1986 (Reel 49, Frame 733)
        - Retreat, 1987 (Reel 49, Frame 817)
        - F. James Rohlf, 1972 (Reel 49, Frame 906)
        - Roper Research Associates, Inc., 1969 (Reel 49, Frame 919)
        - Scandinavian Seminars, 1981 (Reel 49, Frame 947)
        - Robert A. Sellery, Jr., 1972 (Reel 49, Frame 958)
        - Sherry Seward, 1987 (Reel 49, Frame 1,025)
        - Eleanor Shelling, 1980-1983 (Reel 49, Frame 1,029)
        - Stephen J. Smallwood, 1977-1979 (Reel 49, Frame 1,034)
        - Nathaniel W. Spears III, 1968-1975 (Reel 49, Frame 1,048)
        - Special Libraries Association - Catering Contacts, 1974-1975 (Reel 50, Frame 1)
        - Speeches and Papers, 1972-1991 (Reel 50, Frame 11)
        - Speeches and Papers - "America's Voluntary Spirit" - B. O'Connell's Book - Independen Sector Conference, Arlington, Virginia, October 24, 1983 (Reel 50, Frame 61)
        - Speeches and Papers - "Communicating with Foundations" - Meeting of the Council of Deans and Directors Association of American Library Schools, Washington, D. C., January 11, 1979 (Reel 50, Frame 70)
        - Speeches and Papers - "Disclosure, Pro or Con?" - Washington Foundation Luncheon Group, Washington, D. C., February 23, 1979 (Reel 50, Frame 98)
        - Speeches and Papers - "The Foundation Center's Reserve Fund", 1982 (Reel 50, Frame 111)
        - Speeches and Papers - "Impact of Economic Changes on Libraries" - Detroit, Michigan, June 21, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 122)
        - Speeches and Papers - "Remarks by Thomas R. Buckman" - Council of Michigan Foundations, Dearborn, Michigan, February 18, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 180)
        - Speeches and Papers - "Remarks by Thomas R. Buckman" - 29th Annual Conference of the Council on Foundations, Inc., Washington, D. C., May 2, 1978 (Reel 50, Frame 191)
        - Speeches and Papers - Speech - San Francisco, November 28, 1984 (Reel 50, Frame 198)
        - Speeches and Papers - "Texas in The Foundation Center's Publications and Services" - American Library Association Annual Conference, Dallas, Texas, June 26, 1979 (Reel 50, Frame 215)
        - Staff Policies, 1987 (Reel 50, Frame 233)
        - Statement to the Staff, October 18, 1985 (Reel 50, Frame 272)
        - Statistics of Income (SOI) Samples Project, 1985-1986 (Reel 50, Frame 276)
        - Stock Gifts, 1973 (Reel 50, Frame 283)
        - Summaries, 1980-1986 (Reel 50, Frame 286)
        - Summaries, 1987-1993 (Reel 50, Frame 403)
        - Support Test Calculation, 1988 (Reel 50, Frame 542)
        - Yukihisa Suzuki, 1973-1976 (Reel 50, Frame 545)
        - Task Force - New Products, 1985-1986 (Reel 50, Frame 586)
        - Task Force - Program Planning, 1986-1987 (Reel 50, Frame 620)
        - Taxonomy Study - Patricia Read, 1988 (Reel 50, Frame 657)
        - Tracking Meetings, 1981-1982 (Reel 50, Frame 753)
        - Twentiety Century Fund Study, 1980-1983 (Reel 50, Frame 776)
        - User Attitudes Toward Electronic Delivery of Information, 1990 (Reel 50, Frame 826)
        - Washington, D. C. Transition Plan, 1990-1991 (Reel 50, Frame 905)
        - Wingspread Conference, September 14-15, 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 1,050)
        - Work Day Workshop, November 16, 1979 (Reel 50, Frame 1,083)
        - World Studies Data Bank, 1973 (Reel 50, Frame 1,090)
        - Series 1.2A - Administrative Files - Officer and Committee Files - Officer Files - Other Officers Section, undated (Reel 50, Frame 1,108)
      - William Kirsch, 1971-1993; 6
        William Kirsch served as Treasurer of The Foundation Center from 1972-1990.
        - Financial History of The Foundation Center - Floppy Disk, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
          Existence and Location of Copies
          See also Reel 52, Frame 0001.
        - Accounting, 1971-1989 (Reel 50, Frame 1,110)
        - Administrative Committee, 1986 (Reel 50, Frame 1,122)
        - Affiliates, 1981-1985 (Reel 50, Frame 1,125)
        - Agreements, 1977-1993 (Reel 51, Frame 1)
        - American Book Center, Inc., 1985-1986 (Reel 51, Frame 558)
        - American Express Card, 1989 (Reel 51, Frame 576)
        - America's Voluntary Spirit, 1982-1990 (Reel 51, Frame 582)
        - An Annotated Bibliography by Daphne Layton, 1987 (Reel 51, Frame 606)
        - Annual Plan, 1987 (Reel 51, Frame 611)
        - Archival Insurance, 1987-1990 (Reel 51, Frame 615)
        - Archival Projects, 1987-1990 (Reel 51, Frame 627)
        - Archives Project and Proposal, 1985-1987 (Reel 51, Frame 635)
        - Associates Program, 1975-1990 (Reel 51, Frame 649)
        - Association of American Publishers, 1979 (Reel 51, Frame 690)
        - Audits - Peat Marwick - Qualified Opinion, 1974-1976 (Reel 51, Frame 693)
        - Audits - Peat Marwick - Management Letter, 1981-1989 (Reel 51, Frame 716)
        - Better Business Bureau, 1981-1982 (Reel 51, Frame 732)
        - Blue Cross Blue Shield, 1987 (Reel 51, Frame 738)
        - The Board Member's Book, 1984-1986 (Reel 51, Frame 741)
        - Bookstore Sales, 1989 (Reel 51, Frame 748)
        - Gladys Brooks Foundation, 1987-1988 (Reel 51, Frame 751)
        - Burden Foundation Study on Aging, 1986-1987 (Reel 51, Frame 767)
        - Capitalization and Depreciation Policy, 1981 (Reel 51, Frame 770)
        - Cirker's Storage, 1984-1985 (Reel 51, Frame 772)
        - Citibank Leases, 1985-1990 (Reel 51, Frame 775)
        - Complimentary Publications and Services Policy, 1974-1987 (Reel 51, Frame 847)
        - Computerization, 1971-1989 (Reel 51, Frame 865)
        - COMSEARCH, 1985-1987 (Reel 51, Frame 890)
        - Consulting and Honoraria Policy, 1980-1984 (Reel 51, Frame 909)
        - Cooper and Company - National Institutes of Health, 1974-1977 (Reel 51, Frame 917)
        - Copyright Letters, 1976-1981 (Reel 51, Frame 965)
        - Corbel Construction Co., 1987-1988 (Reel 51, Frame 969)
        - Corporate Fund Raising, 1981 (Reel 51, Frame 1,000)
        - Corporate Reference Collection, 1985 (Reel 51, Frame 1,009)
        - Council-Center Relations, 1979-1982 (Reel 51, Frame 1,020)
        - Cushman and Wakefield, 1987 (Reel 51, Frame 1,049)
        - Customized Computer Searches, 1982-1985 (Reel 51, Frame 1,053)
        - Data Bank Allocation Bases, 1983-1986 (Reel 51, Frame 1,096)
        - Databases, 1984-1990 (Reel 51, Frame 1,113)
        - Debt Financing, 1982-1986 (Reel 51, Frame 1,118)
        - DIALOG, 1983-1984 (Reel 51, Frame 1,141)
        - Distribution, 1983-1989 (Reel 51, Frame 1,159)
        - Early Closings, 1989 (Reel 51, Frame 1,195)
        - Employee Benefits, 1975-1989 (Reel 51, Frame 1,199)
        - Fee Charging - Council on Foundations, Inc., 1974-1984 (Reel 51, Frame 1,253)
        - Fee Charging - Custom Searches, 1974-1980 (Reel 51, Frame 1,259)
        - Fee Charging - Mailing Labels, 1977-1980 (Reel 51, Frame 1263)
        - Fee Charging - Non-Custom Searches, 1974 (Reel 51, Frame 1267)
        - Financial History - Introduction, 1991 (Reel 51, Frame 1,271)
        - Financial History of The Foundation Center, 1990-1993 (Reel 52, Frame 1)
          See also floppy disks in Box 1, Folder 2.
        - The Foundation Center - Cleveland Office, 1979-1989 (Reel 52, Frame 216)
        - Foundation Reporting Schedule, 1988 (Reel 52, Frame 293)
        - Fund-Raising - Miscellaneous, 1971-1989 (Reel 52, Frame 297)
        - Fund-Raising Data, 1985-1989 (Reel 52, Frame 334)
        - Grant Handling Procedures, 1988 (Reel 52, Frame 358)
        - Grants as Administrative Expense, 1984-1986 (Reel 52, Frame 360)
        - The Grantsmanship Center, 1983 (Reel 52, Frame 373)
        - Huenefeld Survey, 1981-1989 (Reel 52, Frame 379)
        - Indemnification of Trustees and Officers, 1986 (Reel 52, Frame 478)
        - Independent Sector, 1983-1986 (Reel 52, Frame 483)
        - Information Systems Division, 1982-1990 (Reel 52, Frame 501)
        - Insurance, 1972-1989 (Reel 52, Frame 509)
        - Investment Portfolio, 1972-1992 (Reel 52, Frame 521)
        - The Kresge Foundation, 1990 (Reel 52, Frame 609)
        - M. Day Consultants International, Inc., 1990 (Reel 52, Frame 622)
        - Major Gift Campaign - Campaign Expense, 1986-1988 (Reel 52, Frame 632)
        - Major Gift Campaign - Capital Items, 1988-1989 (Reel 52, Frame 637)
        - Major Gift Campaign - Five-Year Projections, 1988-1991 (Reel 52, Frame 651)
        - Major Gift Campaign - General Chronology, 1985-1992 (Reel 52, Frame 663)
        - Major Gift Campaign - Grants Receivable and Funds Applied Reports, 1987-1992 (Reel 52, Frame 760)
        - Major Gift Campaign - The Robert Woods Johnson Foundation, 1990 (Reel 52, Frame 776)
        - Major Gift Campaign - The Robert Woods Johnson Foundation Annual Grant, 1991-1992 (Reel 52, Frame 817)
        - Major Gift Campaign - The Rockefeller Foundation Grants, 1960-1970 (Reel 52, Frame 837)
        - "Managing for Profit in the Non-Profit World" - Paul Firstenberg, 1986 (Reel 52, Frame 849)
        - Marketing, 1982-1991 (Reel 52, Frame 855)
        - Memoranda, 1986-1992 (Reel 52, Frame 890)
        - The National Directory of Corporate Charity, 1986 (Reel 52, Frame 910)
        - National Guide to Funding in Aging, 1986-1989 (Reel 52, Frame 946)
        - Office Facilities, 1978-1989 (Reel 52, Frame 957)
        - Proposal and Financial History, 1987-1993 (Reel 52, Frame 974)
        - Publication to Congress Program, 1985 (Reel 52, Frame 991)
        - Rapid Growth, 1973-1991 (Reel 52, Frame 1,000)
        - Reserves and Endowments, 1967-1991 (Reel 52, Frame 1,019)
        - Shortfalls and Deficits, 1984-1992 (Reel 52, Frame 1,055)
        - Sweda International, Inc., 1984-1986 (Reel 52, Frame 1,107)
        - Toll-Free Telephone Lines, 1984-1987 (Reel 52, Frame 1,125)
        - Work Papers - The Louis Calder Foundation, 1987 (Reel 52, Frame 1,141)
        - Work Papers - The Commonwealth Fund, 1985 (Reel 52, Frame 1,148)
        - Work Papers - The Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1988 (Reel 52, Frame 1,154)
        - Work Papers - The Rockefeller Foundation, 1987 (Reel 52, Frame 1,188)
        - Work Papers - The Foundation Center - San Francisco, 1984-1988 (Reel 52, Frame 1,196)
        - Xerox, 1982-1988 (Reel 52, Frame 1,216)
      - Marianna O. Lewis, 1945-1982; 7
        Marianna O. Lewis was the first editor of the Foundation Directory (1957-1971). She then became senior research associate (1972-1982) and assistant secretary in 1974.
        - Associates Program, 1974-1975 (Reel 53, Frame 2)
        - Central Intelligence Agency, 1967 (Reel 53, Frame 56)
        - Columbia University Press, 1970-1981 (Reel 53, Frame 87)
        - Computerization, 1967-1971 (Reel 53, Frame 167)
        - Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Reel 53, Frame 261)
        - Correspondence, 1970 (Reel 53, Frame 481)
        - Correspondence, 1971 (Reel 53, Frame 579)
        - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Reel 53, Frame 711)
        - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Reel 53, Frame 886)
        - Correspondence (A-I), 1973-1974 (Reel 53, Frame 1,204)
        - Correspondence (J-Z), 1973-1974 (Reel 54, Frame 1)
        - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Reel 54, Frame 201)
        - Datatab, 1963-1971 (Reel 54, Frame 252)
        - Dikkers Health Foundation, 1962-1969 (Reel 54, Frame 268)
        - Directory of Company-Sponsored Foundations, 1968 (Reel 54, Frame 346)
        - Directory of Evaluations - Mailing List, 1981-1982 (Reel 54, Frame 371)
        - Document Services - Department Manual, undated (Reel 54, Frame 403)
        - Executive Meeting - Transcript of Corporate Contributions, September 3, 1980 (Reel 54, Frame 439)
        - The Foundation Center - Internal Revenue Service Data File, 1971 (Reel 54, Frame 454)
        - The Foundation Center - Internal Revenue Service Data File, 1972 (Reel 54, Frame 486)
        - The Foundation Center - Staff, 1975-1980 (Reel 54, Frame 561)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 1 - Comments, 1960 (Reel 54, Frame 577)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 1 - Connecticut Printers, Inc., 1958-1962 (Reel 54, Frame 593)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 1 - Format for Entries, 1957-1958 (Reel 54, Frame 629)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 1 - Introduction, undated (Reel 54, Frame 637)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 1 - Publicity, 1960 (Reel 54, Frame 740)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 1 - Questionnaires, Forms and Form Letters, 1945-1958 (Reel 54, Frame 773)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 1 - Revisions for Questionnaire and Grants Index, 1960-1964 (Reel 54, Frame 821)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2, 1961-1964 (Reel 54, Frame 855)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Abuses, 1961-1963 (Reel 54, Frame 891)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Accounts, 1961 (Reel 54, Frame 896)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Comments, 1959-1964 (Reel 54, Frame 933)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Complimentary Copies, 1963-1964 (Reel 54, Frame 958)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Connecticut Printers, Inc., 1962-1965 (Reel 54, Frame 992)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Copy to Printer - Knickerbocker Letter Shop, 1962-1963 (Reel 54, Frame 1,015)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Field Work, 1959-1968 (Reel 54, Frame 1,027)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Notes and Indexes, undated (Reel 54, Frame 1,200)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Priliminary Introduction, 1963 (Reel 54, Frame 1,222)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Procedures, 1961-1964 (Reel 54, Frame 1,297)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Publicity, 1962-1965 (Reel 54, Frame 1,325)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Questionnaire, Forms and Form Letters, 1961 (Reel 55, Frame 1)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Sales, 1964-1966 (Reel 55, Frame 18)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Statistics, 1961-1965 (Reel 55, Frame 22)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 - Style Sheet, 1963 (Reel 55, Frame 39)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 2 and 3 - Permissions, 1964-1970 (Reel 55, Frame 59)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 3, 1960-1971 (Reel 55, Frame 197)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 3 - Format for Entries, 1965 (Reel 55, Frame 252)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 3 - Forms and Form Letters, 1964-1968 (Reel 55, Frame 267)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 3 - Introduction, undated (Reel 55, Frame 279)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 3 - Notes, 1963-1967 (Reel 55, Frame 292)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 3 - Publicity, 1967-1970 (Reel 55, Frame 298)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 3 - Special Form Letters, 1966-1967 (Reel 55, Frame 349)